<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Troutary</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Troutary</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">An app for Rainbow Trout Fisheries Research Station</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUs</string>
    <string name="about_Us">


    <b>Background</b>
\n
        \n
        Rainbow Trout Fisheries Station (RTFRS) was established in
        2062 B.S. as Trout Genetic Resource Hatchery Sub-station at
        Dhunche on former abandoned horticulture farm under agriculture
        department of ministry of agriculture to Nepal Agriculture Research
        Council (NARC) and Fisheries Development directorate by using the
        cold water of Trisuli river through canal from Ghatte-khola to
        conduct research on rainbow trout and indigenous aquatic species.
        Since its establishment, this sub-station has worked on extending
        rainbow trout farming, improve hatchability and breeding of trout
        fulfill the demand of trout fingerlings and research on germpalsm
        maintenance of trout. With increasing trend in cold water fish farming
        at temperate region, this sub-station was developed as Agriculture
        Research Station (Fisheries) in 2072 Kartik 12 under Nepal Agriculture
        Research Council for technology generation through research on rainbow
        trout and cold water aquatic species. Later, in fiscal year 2072/73,
        this station was renamed as Rainbow Trout Fisheries Research Station.
        This station lies at Dhunche-8 of Rasuwa district at an altitude of
        approx. 1850 masl.
\n
       \n
        \n
        <b>Goal</b>
\n
        \n

        Enhance livelihood and food security of the nation with increase in production
        and productivity of cold water aquatic species.

\n
        \n
        \n
        <b>Objectives</b>
\n
        \n
The overall objective of this station is to improve the general living condition of the
        farmers of Rasuwa district through increase in fisheries productivity. However the
        specific objective s are:
\n
1.      To conduct research on various aspects of rainbow trout and other aquatic species.
\n
2.      To increase the production and productivity of rainbow trout farming and other aquatic species.
\n
3.      To introduce, evaluate and promote productive aquatic species of temperature region
\n
4.      To develop sustainable aquaculture resource management and production technologies at temperate region.
\n
\n
\n
<b>Strategies
    \n

</b> \n 1.      Identification and selection of appropriate techniques for rainbow trout farming and other aquatic
        species at temperate region
\n
2.      Research on aquaculture at temperate region
\n
3.      Verification of rainbow trout in temperate region
\n

\n
        \n
        \n
        \n

       </string>
    <string name="title_activity_forms">forms</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fisheries">Fisheries</string>
    <string name="fisheries">
        <b><u>Rainbow Trout Fish</u></b>
        \n \n <b>Requirements </b>
 \n \n 1.Water quality and quantity

\n Type: clean and cold
\n Temperature: 10 to 20 degree C
\n PH value: 6.5-8.0
\n Oxygen: above 8 mg/L
\n Water supply: 5 L/sec
\n \n
\n 2.Hatchery

\n Compartment: 36* 35 cm
\n Height: 36+4 cm
\n Length: 215 cm
\n \n
\n 3.Ponds

\n Shape: elongated rectangle
\n Made of: concrete and cement
\n Dimension: 4m* 0.9m*0.5m (depth 0.3 m)
\n Water capacity: 1 ton
\n Fry capacity: 15-20 thousand fry
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="registration">Registration Form</string>
    <string name="internship">Internship Application</string>
    <string name="spinner_title">Nature of raceway</string>

</resources>
